Young Women's Christian Association of Albany, New York; Records apap137
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Files, 1863-1996; 1; 5.26 cubic ft.
  - Membership Cashbook, 1890-1903 (Box 15 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Visitors Book, 1888-1905 (Box 15 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Affidavit of Title, 1913 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Assignment of Mortgage, 1916-1921 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Attendance Lists, Y-Wives, 1974 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Balance Sheets, Undated (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Bonds, 1911-1925 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Budgets, Salary Earnings, Sales Numbers, 1979 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Deeds, 1870-1921 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Endowment Fund, 1970 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Instructor Lists, 1991 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Legal Agreements, 1902-1922 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Mortgages, 1903-1917 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - New York State Resolutions, 1917; 1925; 1957; 1976 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Re-incorporation Agreements, 1963-1972 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Tenant Agreements, 1972 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Warranty Deeds, 1863-1939 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Will and Testaments, 1960-1961; 1970 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - YWCA Construction and Renovation, 1963 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Youth Bureau Agreement and Day Camp Application, 1971-1974 (Box 1A (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Bonds, 1906-1913 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - News Page, Tax Exemptions, 1940 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - Payroll, 1980 December-1989 (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
  - Treasurer Report, Membership Ledger, 1950; 1978; 1989 (Oversized 2, Folder 4)
  - Trial Balance, 1981-1988 (Oversized 2, Folder 5)
- Board and Committee Files, 1930-1995; 2; 2.39 cubic ft.
  This series is comprised of meeting minutes, treasury reports, and correspondence from 1930 to 1995. Minutes are from the Board of Directors, Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, and various other committees within the organization. Annual Meeting minutes are also included.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically.
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1966 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Association Review Committee, National Review Team, 1970-1979 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Ballots, 1972; 1977 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors Budget Reports, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, By-laws, Undated (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence, 1968-1978 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1935-1936 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1937 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1939-1941 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1949-1951 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 1 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, Undated (Box 3 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, and Officer Liability Insurance, 1985-1992 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors, Officer Lists, 1959-1990; Undated (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors, Orientation, 1992 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors, Reports and Balance Sheets, 1953 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, Responsibilities, Undated (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, Statement of Assets and Liabilities, 1978 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1928-1944 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 4 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1980-1982 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1985 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, Treasury Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, Trial Balance, 1980 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees, Correspondence, 1980-1988 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1933-1964 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1990-1995 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees, Officer Lists and Organizational Structure, 1983-1989 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees, Responsibilities, Undated (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, Retirement Fund, 1976-1990 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Cafeteria Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1944-1951 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Cafeteria Committee, Reports, 1944-1951 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Centennial Committee Guide for Commemoration, 1955 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Centennial Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - Committee and Job Descriptions, Undated (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 10)
  - Department Report, 1963 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 11)
  - Executive Board, Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1933-1936 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1937-1941 (Box 6 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1969-1970; 1973-1975 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1979-1984 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1985-1989 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 7)
  - Executive and Finance Committee, Meeting Minutes, Advisors and Building Committee Meeting Minutes, 1964 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 8)
  - Finance Committee, Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1983-1994 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 9)
  - Finance Committee, Notes, 1930-1933 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 10)
  - Finance Manuals and Treasury Responsibilities, Undated (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 11)
  - Health Department Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1959 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 12)
  - House Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1934-1945 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 13)
  - Membership Committee, Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 14)
  - National YWCA, Meeting Minutes Concerning Tax Legislation, 1979 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 15)
  - National YWCA Board, Treasurer's Report, 1980-1981 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 16)
  - Nominating Committee, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1984-1988 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 17)
  - Race Relations Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 18)
  - Residence Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 19)
  - Resource Development Committee, Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1979 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 20)
  - Staff and Board of Directors Workshop, 1986 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 21)
  - Staff Meeting, Minutes and Agendas, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 22)
  - Supervisory Group Report, 1990 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 23)
  - Thursday Afternoon Club, Federated Business and Professional Club Papers (from scrapbook), 1939-1940 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 24)
  - Tribute Committee Report, 1985 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 25)
  - Various Committee Meeting Minutes, 1962-1974 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 26)
  - World Fellowship Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1959-1963 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 27)
  - World Fellowship Committee, Meeting Minutes, Undated (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 28)
  - Youth Committee Meeting, 1978 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 29)
  - YWCA Organizational Cart, 1987 (Box 7 (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors, Treasurer's Report, 1981 (Box 1A (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 19)
  - Tribute Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 1A (2-Board and Committee Files), Folder 20)
- Public Relations, Programs, and Events, 1911-1995; 3; 1.22 cubic ft.
  This series documents the YWCA programs, newsletters and special events from 1911 to 1995. Materials include class offerings, Black History Month essay contest programs and essays, annual Tribute to Women award ceremony materials, brochures, and fliers.
  - Albany YWCA Health Parade Bulletins, 1940 (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - American Women; 1607 to Present, 6 volumes, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - The Association Hymnal, 1926 (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - Black History Month Essay Contest, 1985-1991 (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - Brochures, Fliers, and Programs, 1911-1939 (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - Brochures, Fliers, and Programs, 1940-1949 (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - Brochures, Fliers, and Programs, 1959-1984 (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - Brochures, Fliers, and Programs, Undated (Box 1 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - Brochures of Workshops and Classes, 1977-1982; Undated (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - Brochures of Workshops and Classes, 1983-1987 (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - Brochures of Workshops and Classes, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - Brochures of Workshops and Classes, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - Brochures of Workshops and Classes, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - Federated Business Girls Club, Programs and Newsletters, 1939 (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - Fliers (non-Albany related), 1941-1949; 1958 (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - Guest Book, 1979 (Box 2 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - Guest Book, Undated (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 1)
  - In Behalf of Working Women, YWCA Record, Undated (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 2)
  - The Industrial Awakening and the YWCA, 1920 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 3)
  - Introducing the YWCA to New Members, 1937 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 4)
  - Life Process Center for Women, Undated (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 5)
  - Music, Let's Have More of It, 1960 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, 1940 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 7)
  - Our Faith and Ourselves Today, 1955 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs in the YWCA, 1957 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 9)
  - Public Affairs Newsletters and Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 10)
  - Skits and Songs, Undated (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 11)
  - Thursday Afternoon Club, Programs, ca. 1940s (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 12)
  - Tribute to Women, Biographies, Undated (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 13)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony Programs, 1979-1985 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 14)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 15)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony Programs, 1988-1990 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 16)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony Programs, 1991-1994 (Box 3 (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 17)
  - Citation and Resolution of 100th Anniversary, 1988 (Box 1A (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 21)
  - Black History Month Certificate and Proclamation, 1990 (Box 1A (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 22)
  - Display Descriptions, Undated (Box 1A (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 23)
  - Member Certificate, 1909 (Box 1A (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 24)
  - Newsletter, 1940 (Box 1A (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 25)
  - Proclamation, YWCA of Albany Month, 1988 (Box 1A (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 26)
  - Winter 1998 Program, Rough Draft, 1988 (Box 1A (3-Public Relations, Programs, and Events), Folder 27)
  - African American History Month Proclamation, 1994 (Oversized 2, Folder 6)
  - The Albany Review, 1989 (Oversized 2, Folder 7)
  - Citation, 1988 (Oversized 2, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers, 1974; 1989 (Oversized 2, Folder 9)
  - Poster American Women, 1983 (Oversized 2, Folder 10)
  - Poster Women Veterans, Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 11)
  - Posters Women's History Week, Undated (Oversized 2, Folder 12-16)
- News Clippings and Scrapbook Material, 1905-1995; 4; 0.99 cubic ft.
  This series consists of photocopies of news clippings and scrapbook materials pertaining to the Albany YWCA and/or collected by the Albany YWCA from 1905 to 1995. Whenever possible, the original order of the scrapbooks is maintained, which does not always correspond with chronological order. Loose news clippings and loose scrapbook pages are organized by date. Original items in scrapbooks, such as programs, photographs, postcards, and letters are filed separately within the series.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - News Clippings, 1905-1925 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1930-1939 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1940-1949 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1950-1959 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1960-1974 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1982-1989 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1991-1995 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, Poster Photocopy, 1994 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, ca. 1950s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, ca. 1990s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, Undated (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, Thursday Afternoon Club, Undated (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, Originals, ca. 1910s-1940s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook, Photocopies, ca. 1910s-1940s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook, Originals, ca. 1930s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook, Originals, ca. 1930s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook, Photo Album, ca. 1930s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook, Photo Album, ca. 1930s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook, Loose Pages and News Clippings, ca. 1930s-1960s (Box 1 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 20)
  - Scrapbook, Loose Pages and News Clippings, ca. 1957-1959; Undated (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1932-1936 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1937-1938 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1938-1939 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1939 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1939 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1939-1940 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, Originals, 1939-1949 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, Photocopies, 1939-1949 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, Originals, Publicity Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, Publicity Reports, Photocopies, 1940-1941 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1940 (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, Originals, ca. 1940s (Box 2 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, Thursday Afternoon Club, 1940-1941 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, Business and Professional Club, 1941-1942 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, Girls Reserve, 1941-1945 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1950-1954 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, Outing Club, Originals, 1952-1953 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, Outing Club, Photocopies, 1952-1953 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1954 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, 1956-1958 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, 1962-1963 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook, 1962-1963 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1964 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1965 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook, 1965-1967 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook, 1981-1983 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook, 1983-1985 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook, 1986-1989 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 17)
  - Scrapbook, 1990-1993 (Box 3 (4-News Clippings and Scrapbook Material), Folder 18)
- Photographs, 1911-1995; 5; 2.64 cubic ft.